componentbuy.com 2016-05-02

# Component Buy

## Privacy Ploicy

Componentbuy ("we" or "us") consider protection of your privacy and personal information with great regard. We have framed the privacy policy to inform you about Componentbuy practices. By visiting and using the Componentbuy services or registering with the Componentbuy and creating an account, you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this privacy policy ("Privacy Policy").

## What This Privacy Policy Covers

This Privacy Policy describes Componentbuy's practices with respect to Personal Information and Anonymous Information that we collect when you use Componentbuy.

We collect "Personal Information" when you register or request other information from us like names, addresses, e-mail addresses, or phone numbers, as well as other non-public information. This information is used to ensure a quick, efficient flow of products and services to you. Your personal information are never rented, sold or traded to third parties.

We collect "Anonymous Information" like click-stream data such as referring URL, browser and platform, time of visit, pages visited and searches performed. These data is gathered to help us improve the performance of our website and offer better services to you. We analyze this data to establish trends and help us improve your online experience. Aggregated data may be used to solicit ads from potential advertisers and business partners. This data will be used in strict conformity with our privacy policy.

We collect and use Personal Information and Anonymous Information as described in this Privacy Policy from users of the Componentbuy ("users"). By using our services or submitting personal information through the service, you expressly consent to the processing of your personal information according to this privacy policy.

## Use of Cookies

Componentbuy website collects Anonymous Information concerning website users through the use of "cookies" in order to provide better customer service. "Cookies" are files that websites place on users' computers to identify the user and enhance the website experience. If you choose not to accept a cookie, you will still be able to use our website.
